Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- In our suburbs.
evil lurks behind closed doors...
True stories so terrifying
because the horror is real.
You will never look at your
neighbors the same way again.
I'm John Carpenter.
and this is
"Suburban Screams."
- I regret ever playing
with that Ouija board.
I wish I wouldn't have.
and this would have
never happened.
My name's Dan.
Back in 1999. I moved
out of my parents' home
into this bungalow house
that I rented at the time
in Nepean. Ontario.
The neighborhood was friendly.
It was very close community.
very tight.
Not a lot of spaces
between the houses.
of course.
because it's very suburban.
Not a lot of cars going by.
so there's a lot of kids
playing in the street.
I felt very safe
in that neighborhood.
It was a nice neighborhood
to live in.
I needed to just
re-center myself.
'cause I went through
a lot of emotional stress
when my dad died of cancer.
Um. girlfriend at the time
had an addiction
that I couldn't get her
off that addiction.
It was a hard time in my life.
Very hard.
- Jesus. Becky.
- Don't start now.
- All I spent on your rehab.
and look at you.
If you're looking for money.
you're not gonna find any.
No. no.
I'm sorry.
I'm so...
- I can't do this. Becky.
I can't help you anymore.
- No. No.
- Becky. Becky. Becky.
- Fuck it.
- I tried to put her in detox
on three occasions
where she came out
kind of sober for a little bit
and then went back
to the addiction.
I could see that
she was spiraling down.
and I wanted to help her.
but there was nothing
I could do.
I don't know.
It... it all happened. like...
Excuse me.
It's just...
Seeing my. father die of cancer
was. um...
the most horrible thing
I ever experienced.
And having a girlfriend
that had a drug addiction
didn't help either. you know?
It's... it's a feeling
of helplessness.
I couldn't stop her
from doing what she was doing.
I... I broke off with her.
I said. "I'm done.
"I need a fresh start.
I need to restart my life.
And I'm not doing this
anymore."
And that's when Joey moved in.
- No chance!
- I rented a room
in the basement from him
in the burbs. you know?
There was always something
going on in the house.
My God!
- When I first met in May.
it wasn't a lot of. like.
courtship or anything.
We kind of clicked.
and...
And it just built up from there.
- Last beers in the house.
You're an angel.
- And I'm the devil.
- Hey. you ever used
a Ouija board?
- The toy?
- No. it's kind of a...
My brother used to use it
to freak me out
when we were kids...
until I figured out he was just
pushing the pointer thingy.
- The planchette.
My God. do you have one?
- No. I don't.
but I could make one.
- Ooh. Here we go.
Got the beers.
- Awesome.
- To the ghosts.
Okay.
So I need everybody
to gently place their
middle and index fingers
onto the planchette.
So everybody...
Now close your eyes...
And clear your mind.
We call upon the spirit world
and welcome any spirits
to talk with us.
Spirits. if you are here.
please talk with us.
- This is stupid.
I'm sorry.
Grandma?
Is that you?
Still racist as ever?
Shit. Grandma.
I was just joking.
Asshole!
Grandma!
- I'm sorry.
- Don't touch me.
- Done.
- No. Look. I'll be serious.
Come on.
We'll be serious.
- Hey. look.
you can even ask the questions.
All right?
All right. Come on.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna kill you.
We call upon the spirit world.
- We call upon the spirit world
and welcome any spirits
to talk to us.
Ask the spirits for a name.
- Okay.
Is someone here now?
Can you tell us your name?
Dan?
- I'm not doing it.
- Joey?
- I swear
I'm not fucking around.
- This is crazy.
- It spelled Kelly.
Does anybody know a Kelly?
- I... I think we should stop.
Stop it!
Shit.
- What the fuck?
My God.
- You're such a prick.
It was...
it was a little hard
to comprehend. honestly.
It was... it was strange.
It was a really strange feeling.
- The girls were upset that
we played a trick on 'em.
And we looked at them and said.
"No. no. the lamp we did.
"That was deliberate.
But the chairs were not."
May was tearful.
Actually.
she had tears in her eyes.
I remember that.
- Are you okay?
I mean. it's freaking me out.
- Um. I had a cousin
named Kelly.
Kelly Fitzgerald.
We were really close
when we were little.
But as we grew up. she started
getting into coke and speed
and who knows what else.
She was hanging out
with some very seedy people.
It got really dark.
- I'm so sorry.
- She was like a sister to me.
you know?
And then she wasn't.
She went missing
a long time ago.
I don't know
what happened to her.
- So now I'm going.
"Okay. what's going on?"
It got a little more serious
because now we're actually
connecting with actual people
that existed.
that actually had a life
and they lived.
There's something that's
starting to happen here.
- You question your sanity
at that point.
And you wonder. like.
am I going crazy?
Should I go see a doctor?
Should I go see a psychiatrist?
Like. what's going on?
Is there really something
after death?
Is it possible that something
from the other side
can communicate with us?
- Hey.
I'm on the internet.
- What's up?
- I'm searching to find out
about your cousin Kelly.
- Like what?
I told you.
She got with some bad people.
Like. really. really bad.
- And then?
I mean. she couldn't have
just disappeared. right?
Maybe something happened to her.
Don't you want to find out?
I'd rather not.
The whole thing just
kind of makes me sad.
- What if she needs our help?
Come on. Dan.
Are... are you even serious
right now?
You think you're trying
to help a... a ghost?
- I just think maybe
we could try it one more time.
You know?
The Ouija board?
You know there are other Kellys
out there besides my cousin.
Why do you think it was her?
- Maybe it wasn't.
Maybe it was.
I don't know.
Look. just... just one last time?
I promise.
- Whatever.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
- Wait.
- May said. like. "Stop
playing with this stuff. guys.
This is not something
to be messing around with."
But of course.
we kept going anyways.
because it's what we do. right?
We keep... we keep
messing around with stuff...
Which was a bad idea.
- Nope. this is all you.
- We call upon the spirit world
and welcome any spirits
to talk with us.
Spirits.
if there is anyone here.
please let us know.
Kelly... are you here?
Are you May's cousin?
Please give us a sign.
Daniel...
- I coughed. and...
what I thought was water
came out of my mouth.
It just flew out of my mouth.
- Jesus. Dan. are...
Are you okay?
I saw...
I saw her.
I...
I felt her drowning.
I could feel it.
I could feel her drowning.
- It was all very real
at that point.
This was real.
She was real.
- When that happened.
I thought that maybe
there was more to the story.
It was almost like she was
trying to tell me something.
- After we had
the contact with Kelly
with the Ouija board.
like. the idea of this person
somehow just sort of
became a big part of the house.
Most conversations
revolved around her.
It was an emotional time.
- She's trying
to show me something.
- Why?
Why you. Dan?
- I don't know.
I just feel it.
I just feel it. like... like
she needs my help or something.
you know?
- Maybe she wants to kill you
or me or everyone in this house.
I'm really scared!
- Look. babe. I'm scared too.
But you gotta listen to me
when...
- No. no. no. I'm done. okay?
No more Ouija boards.
No more visions.
No more Kelly.
If she is dead.
let her rest in peace.
- Let her rest in peace.
- I felt like I owed Kelly
something for some reason.
I don't know this girl.
I felt like
I owed her something.
like I was compelled
to do something
to try to solve and figure out
what happened to her.
Because my gut feeling
was saying that
there's more to this story
that's not coming out.
After that.
there was a song that...
It was like a connection
to Kelly.
Every time that song would play
or that specific song
would play.
it seems that
that's when stuff would happen.
It's like opening up a handle
or a door or something.
If you listen to the lyrics.
you could imagine
somebody who's passed away
of a tragic death
trying to communicate
with somebody now living.
that this is
what they would say.
- Dan.
- She was in the car with me.
Just following me everywhere.
like just an attachment.
I felt like
I was losing my sanity.
Like. why is this happening?
Like. why am I getting
these visions?
It just didn't make any sense.
- Wait.
Kelly.
Wait. Wait.
Kelly!
- Kelly.
Daniel.
Kelly?
- Daniel. help me.
- After the incident in the car.
May came to find me.
- What happened?
- I saw her.
- Don't lose it on me. Dan.
- This is the song.
This is the song.
Listen to the words.
"Will you find me?"
Listen to it.
"A way to die?"
- They play this song.
like. 20 times a day.
- Just... just listen to it.
all right?
It's a cry for help.
My God.
You're obsessed.
- How could you be
so fucking heartless?
- I can't... I can't do this.
Get out.
Get out!
- Look. I'm getting close.
- Close to what?
- Helping Kelly.
- You're losing your mind.
Get out!
Please. just go!
- She was not happy.
So we did not leave
on good terms.
and never spoke to her after.
- Jesus.
Daniel.
- No. no.
No! No!
- Dan?
Dan?
Jesus. Dan.
You all right?
- You gotta stop drinking.
- Leave me alone.
- Let me help you.
- No. Leave. leave. leave.
Get out.
- Dude. let me help you.
- Fucking... fucking leave!
- Dude. I'm just trying to help!
- Okay. Go.
- It all seemed to be a lot
to take in for him. I guess.
It caused an
obsession with him...
The Kelly. the music.
the house. Ouija.
And it... it became
what it was all about.
- After that.
I spent months by myself
locked in my basement trying
to communicate with Kelly.
But nothing really happens.
you know?
How can I help you
if you won't talk to me?
Talk to me.
Just talk to me. Kelly.
Tell me how to help you!
I can't help you
unless you talk to me.
What the fuck
do you want from me?
Talk to me.
Fuck!
- The emotions would
become very intense.
almost so emotional that...
So sad. like sadness.
Yep. just...
I think with Kelly.
it was that third thing that...
Somebody else
that I couldn't help.
I couldn't help my father.
I couldn't do anything.
He was dying.
Um. my girlfriend.
I tried to put her in detox
as many times as I could
to get her off the drugs.
And then Kelly.
I just couldn't stop
thinking about her.
It was like it was becoming
part of me.
- Kelly?
- And I felt so bad
for this girl
that I couldn't do
anything for her.
And I wanted to.
And I felt obsessed
that I had to.
- Kelly?
Kelly!
Kelly.
I know you're here. Kelly.
Kelly. Kelly.
Where are you?
Kelly. I know you're here!
Show yourself.
- I had a vision of the night
that Kelly disappeared.
This guy was fairly tall.
probably about close to 6 feet.
thin. baldheaded...
Almost. like. just no hair.
and this makeshift
homemade tattoo
of a heart on his chest.
Then I saw another guy
doing drugs.
And then things got
out of hand with her.
- I know who did it. Joey.
- What? Who did what?
- The bald man with a tattoo
and that other freak.
they killed her.
- Bald man with a tattoo?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
- They killed Kelly.
- Jesus. Dan.
- I'm sure of it.
They put her in a sleeping bag
or something. and then...
I've seen it. I've seen it.
- When?
When did this happen?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
But I've just seen it
with my own eyes.
You know what?
I'm gonna go to the police.
- You're gonna go to the police
and tell them that?
Are you out of your mind?
- One of the reasons
I've never spoken
about this story
is because I don't want
to be implicated in this.
you know. especially with
the kind of evidence I have
is all feelings.
Ouija board sessions.
- There's gotta be something
I can do to help her.
I have to help her.
Don't you get it?
- To me. it's like.
no. I'll just be ridiculed.
I'll look like a fool.
I... I just didn't know
what to do.
I felt like I... I... I...
I needed to find out
what happened that night.
So I decided to consult
with a psychic medium.
Her name was Manuela.
I told her the whole story
about Kelly.
And she said what's going on
is that Kelly is a spirit
kind of like in limbo.
She doesn't know she's dead.
And right now... and this was
the weirdest thing for me...
She said. "Now she's developed
a love attachment for you."
And I go. "Excuse me?
A love attachment?"
"Yes. this girl is
attached to you.
"and she wants you to help her.
"and you're gonna
have to let her know
"that she's passed away.
You're gonna have
to help her move on."
And that's what
I tried to do after that
is just try to get her
to move on.
because my sense of guilt
for not being able
to do something for her
really was so intense.
That's... that doesn't go away.
- This is the place.
Kelly. where are you?
Kelly?
- Daniel.
- Not possible.
You're not alive. Kelly.
- Help me. Daniel.
- You're not alive.
You have to believe me.
You were murdered.
You're not alive.
- Stay with me. Daniel.
- I can't.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Jesus. man.
You all right?
- She's right there.
She's right there!
Go. Go.
Just go!
- What the hell?
- There's a dead girl in here!
There's a dead girl in here!
- It was designated
a drug overdose cause of death
and that likely what happened.
the people she was with panicked
and didn't know what to do.
So they actually wrapped
her body in a sleeping bag
and dumped her body
instead of reporting it.
That's what the investigation
assumed happened.
because obviously. she...
Somebody put her there.
But no. it was not correct.
That was a murder.
Because nobody dumps a body
and then takes off.
It's an unsolved mystery. right?
- Everybody was left with
different emotions after that.
Um. I was convinced.
Um. there was no telling me
that it wasn't real
at that point. you know?
It was to me.
It was to Dan.
It was our story.
It was our life.
We lived it. We... we...
It's hard to wrap
your head around.
- I would like
Kelly's case solved.
I don't think
I'll ever find peace
until we find out exactly
what happened that night.
And I think right now.
I think that's why
I'm sitting in this chair.
It's...
Very sad.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org